

CONTACT

- +593998651891
- luiseducol13egmail.com
- https://the-lu.vercel.app/

SKILLS

- Designer web
- Nextis
- Svelte
- Creativity
- persistent
- Good leader
- Designer ux/ui
- Problem solving

LANGUAGE

- Spanish Native
- English A2

Technology

HTML, CSS, JQuery, NodeJS, Express, (NoSQL), Git, Heroku, GitHub, Bootstrap, Sequealize, PostgreSQL, Reactjs, Nextjs, Svelte, Nextui, Paypal, BinancePay.

LUISANGEL TAPIA

Full Stack Developer

Junior programmer hungry for success, hard working and always trying to find the most innovative way possible, always taking each task or project to its maximum expression. In fact, a junior programmer with few experiences but with great expectations about the technological world.

EDUCATION

2022- 2023 Full Stack Devoloper. Academlo.

2012-2020 Medium Technician in Machine and Tools. E.T.I "Joaquin Avellan"

EXPERIENCE

Worind Guayaquil, Ecuador 2022 Designe web

Worind Guayaquil, Ecuador 2021 - August 2022 Milling Turner , CNC Programmer August

Sincatesa Maracay, Aragua, Venezuela Enero 2020 - Marzo 2020 CNC Programmer

Main projects

Ecommerce ResApi

Create in BACKEND of an ecommers in 5 days
We developed an Ecommers-API with stylized cart
functions using express as a nodejs framework.

Ecommers Frontend

Create an ecommerce in 7 days with React with shopping cart functionalities.

Blnance Pay Web

Implement Binance's payment method for product sales or ecommerce. Made with nextJS. without any reference where you can read only the Binance website. NextUI Implementation.